Welcome back guys, welcome back to a new week.
Welcome back to a new vlog.
Today is Tuesday, the 2nd of June, and it is a pretty special day because
today is my boyfriend's birthday.
It's now midday.
I started the day, of course, with a little breakfast in bed.
I think it's like bare minimum, right?
When it's someone's birthday.
And I planned a few surprise this week.
One of them being us going to Florence this Friday.
So I'm super excited to spend the weekend there.
And tonight I'm actually, no, he's not here.
Tonight I'm actually inviting a few of his friends for a little surprise aperitif to
celebrate his birthday since we're going to be together the whole weekend i was like
let's just do something fun tonight on the day of his birthday with his friends
um there is going to be a huge roland garros match of the brazilian joan
fonseca which i know he really wants to watch so basically it's going to be
champagne burgers roland garros and friends and i feel like it's a vibe but before
we get to the birthday party parts organizing which have a lot to do still.
I have to go to an eyewear presentation of the Kering group, which I'm so
excited because they have so many brands I love.
And then I have a modeling job.
Then I run back here.
So let's get dressed.
It's a gloomy day today, so I feel like I can wear black.
I'm gonna wear these black kind of slouchy Beckenbridge jeans.
For the top, I'm gonna wear this gorgeous backless top by beck and bridge but
it's still very like closed up in the front so i feel like it's perfect
for a day event with slouchy jeans it's kind of still chic but not you
know too much it's like this oh that's cute back is so pretty but
yeah for daytime i feel like it looks cool let's see nice love it so
that's what it looks like oh it looks really nice because it's cinched here and
then it goes like kind of hourglass effect with the balloon type of denim and
then the back that's perfect heel boot you know it's gonna be
perfect with this look my little verified clutch because it's black and silver so it's
gonna go perfectly with my look I love it because it's a clutch it's very
chic but it has the handle and it still looks kind of cool and you
know elevated and big enough to have enough things I'm gonna quickly add a little
bit of pink to my lips just to add some color that's a little bit
missing let me touch my under eye i've been loving this merit
complexion stick to have in my bag whenever i need a touch-up just because see
it's sinking to the skin super quickly so it's kind of the type of products
you want when you want to do a touch-up it's something that corrects well so
you brought a lot of light but it's easy to kind of pop on at
any spots this is shade linen it's pretty fair in here
we are ready the sisters are reunited and we're kind of matching which wasn't planned
Hi
guys!
And we're now walking to the eyewear event, which I'm honestly very excited because I
love eyewear.
We love eyewear.
Eyewear does everything.
Like, our lives...
Look, look, look, plain.
Look, plain.
Aha!
Now it's working.
I have someone from the community, a very loyal person from the community that said
from the community that said i sent you and karen to velia eyewear so that
they should take you to promote their sunglasses another cutest thing ever so cute
that looks amazing
oh that's pretty oh that is pretty oh that no super
What do you think?
It's really good These are my favorite and I know my sister is gonna love
this
They're gorgeous I'm gonna try these
I wanna try these because I think they can be incredible for summer with a
little bikini
You guys, I just got out of my
modern fitting and remember we wrapped from this.
I think this is not supposed to happen.
It's unwrapping.
Oh my god, the weather is insane.
I just got out of my fitting and I have a thousand things to do
to prepare for the birthday.
Look at this.
I feel like I'm the weather girl.
Yeah, so I have a thousand things to do to prepare for the birthday and
I'm honestly feeling a little sleepy So I'm gonna grab a little cappuccino at Cova.
They have it right in front of where I work
I'll get you a cappuccino please No, not yet, the classic one Yes, classic
Thank you very much
So
I am walking to Guerrilla Faiyat Gourmet, which is a department store, but
across the road they have a department store for food.
And that's where I'm going because my boyfriend's favorite cake is the opera, which is
a type of chocolate cake.
And because they have so many different pastry corners, I would say, I'm probably going
to find it there.
That was like my best option to find.
And then I just realized I have to pick up a gift too because we
did a group gift and so many other things.
And I'm like, oh my God, I have two hours left.
Look at this.
This is desserts.
How crazy.
They look so perfect.
This is a cheesecake.
This is a tiramisu.
How cute!
So basically this whole place is sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.
Look at this huge pain au chocolat.
Okay, I'm gonna get this because this is the post to a opera.
Tension is high.
So he left the apartment.
I got one of his friends to call him up last minute and be like,
let's go have a drink for your birthday.
But instead of leaving at 530, he left at almost 630 and everyone's arriving at
like 745.
and so I didn't have much time to prepare so I just literally ran out
of the house bought everything and um hopefully I'm ready on time I still would
like to do my hair get dressed uh but I still have a lot of
things to prepare I have to pack the gift I mean I am waiting on
my sister Lisa where are you I'm waiting on her because she was supposed to
come and help me and I'm like I need you right I am with the
sister.
Thankfully she arrived to help me.
We're preparing.
It's cute cute.
We're preparing plenty of little things.
So I did kind of a little bar station.
We'll have champagne and you can have some cheese.
I love this little plate.
I've been using it so much.
And then over there I added some more glasses and just some more of like
dried snacks because i feel it's easier to eat if you're sitting i am wearing
this little blue dress which fun fact last year right at this time of my
boyfriend's birthday was our first two weeks of dating so basically his birthday was our
fourth date and at the time i was like well you know we don't know
each other much so do whatever you want for your birthday.
And he was like, no, I want to spend my birthday with you.
and i was super stressed because i was like that was already a green flag
i was like how well that was a great green flag true i was like
how do i like how do i plan a birthday to someone that i barely
know and we ended up having such a great evening i organized a dinner at
vivant de which was like really cool and like good vibes and i wore this
dress and he always talks about the blue dress And today I was like, so
I've been lying all day.
Please, someone give me an Oscar.
I was like, I don't know what to wear tonight because the place we're going
is super fancy.
And he's like, wear the blue dress, wear the blue dress.
So since we're home and the place is not fancy fancy, I'm wearing the blue
dress.
Good morning, guys.
It is bright and early.
It's 8 a.m.
I am in a neighborhood called Saint-Denis, I think.
Yes.
And the party was a success.
I didn't go to bed till late.
It was around midnight, so it was perfect because some of them wanted to party.
And I was like, please go.
I have things to do tomorrow.
I am actually heading out to a photo shoot.
So here I am.
It's only half day, which is great.
So this afternoon I'll get to work on Twin Flame and things like that.
I am so happy.
My boyfriend was so surprised.
Surprise accomplished.
And yeah.
And today I have a really fun thing that I'm going to do.
And we're going to do together.
Because, I don't know, I wanted a special dress for Florence.
And I'm going to a place where I get to try on plenty of dresses
and rent one for the weekend.
So we're going there with Lisa at the end of the day today.
so we'll do that together but in the meantime it is photo shoot time white
t-shirt blue jeans this bag cutest thing ever so simple and ready to get to
hair and makeup if i'm in the right place
makeup done and i am waiting to be called on set we're still going to
do a little picture to see if the makeup looks good on camera and then
we start shading The sisters are together again.
Well, not again.
Dressed the same.
We did not.
It's embarrassing.
We did not plan this again.
Like, what are you wearing on your feet?
White t-shirts and a black and silver bag yeah
and out of the little sister moment yes as a as
i'm gonna be a helper she's gonna be a helper that's my only role i'm
going to italy this weekend for my boyfriend's birthday and on saturday night we're eating
at a really beautiful place and i was in the mood to have a really
nice piece to wear and i've been looking for something for the past weeks but
i haven't found anything where I was like oh that's absolutely it and I'm gonna
spend my money on that yeah and then I reminded myself of Lisa's spot that
she had found recently called rent-a-club in Paris where they've never been I just saw
it oh yeah it's a place where you can go and you can rent a
dress for a day or two but which the concept yeah already absolutely there is
that they have cool brands like fancy club like mesh key like things we actually
like to Here's the look.
White, white, leather, leather, blue jeans.
And sneakers and silver bags.
You're going to take it?
Yes, it's good.
Oh, it's there!
we're
set up downstairs this is the little dressing room that i get to play with
okay so this is the fancy club dress that i wanted to try so option
number one look one look number one fancy club it's so pretty it's so
pretty option number two fancy club again this black dress love the little roses details
it's a tiny bit too big yeah i wish but the cut is cool option
number three fancy club not the vibe the dolce the vibe but we love the
look for her birthday.
How cute is this?
Yeah, I love that.
It's actually also a vintage shop and Lisa just found a big gorgeous blue dress.
Cute.
C'est sublime.
Makes your eyes pop.
It's the color of the season.
Turquoise.
Yeah.
Tiffany blue is the color of the season.
Pala.
Take it.
Oh, it's gorgeous with your aqua Zura shoes new one the blue ones insane
Chanel
Just said to him in French I said visit it I was supposed to go
with you and Just be you know an assistant and I ended up buying something.
She bought the dress
the dress i said if i don't have any options for this weekend lisa
has money and i'm gonna go shop her closet any movie you can vlog it
oh i can vlog it oh she gives me the permission i'll do it like
in-store experience you'll have to book your appointment yes i will come and then you
know oh that's i'll put my boyfriend to be like the you know like do
you want a drink oh do you want glass of champagne a glass of champagne
that's nice i like that so here we are so basically love the white dress
it was exactly what i wanted sexy but still dolce vita vibes right with a
little pair of mules it would have been perfect but the person that rented it
before me effed it up put makeup stained it she went on a wild party
and really did disrespected It's the person, the dress, the dress and the brand.
So she's going to try to get it completely cleaned.
If it get cleaned, I will rent it.
If not, I'm going naked.
But that, right now, you know what's happening in my mind?
I'm going to go on fancy club and I'm going to buy something.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because everything I tried from them was insane.
Oh, c'est magnifique, look at this guys.
The sexy girl that you see right in between the buildings.
How beautiful.
I love it.
It's beautiful.
Look, I can zoom more.
Oh, wow.
Good afternoon, guys.
I am with the sister again.
We've reunited because I came to shop her closet because I have nothing to wear
for my trip tomorrow.
And I'm kind of thinking now, do I have something for her?
I don't know.
We'll see.
We'll find it.
anyway we had lunch together and we went to kmart and we were in the
queue and i saw this it's jeju matcha almond almond so it's like almond
covered no almond covered with matcha and i discovered this three years ago because one
of my really good friends in bali she would travel often to korea and she
would bring this back to me she was like you need to try this and
it was delicious.
So when I saw it, I was like, we need to buy it.
But Lisa has never tried it, so it's the tastiest.
C'est très bon.
I love almonds and dark chocolate.
C'est pas dark chocolate.
I think it's white, or maybe not, or nothing.
C'est bon, hein?
And you know what?
It's those things.
The first one is okay, and then the second and the third is even better
you know what it's white chocolate no it's not you don't think so no super
sweet it's sweet but there is no white chocolate
it's good
there is no chocolate
so you approve oh yeah it's good welcome to lisa's closet welcome to the closet
I'm looking for options.
So here we have dresses.
We have long dresses.
You have this green one?
I have this green one.
When did you buy this?
Very long time ago.
Oh I have this green one.
But I think it's ripped.
Okay this one I thought of because you wore it a lot but I've never
worn it.
I wore it so much I can't even see it.
It's a long dress v-neck i feel like it can be useful just take it
i won't take it anyway perfect dress number one is this rat and boa yeah
archive that's the archive rat and boa that's when rat and boa started they used
to do that was prints with like this velvet and it was so pretty it's
very romantic it's dolce vita vibes you know what i just wish it was different
i just wish it was a different style I think but that's a timeless side
no pretty sad is she reclamation but very romantic no it looks great because you
have big boobs doesn't look good on small boobs it's true there are some dresses
right they look great when you have big boobs and if you have small boobs
so here we have dresses that can't be hung that is to see that long
one see if you just just she'll revolve oh are you wearing that no I'm
not wearing up that could be an option it's oh that's very chic but it's
a one sleeve but it is gorgeous back
that's kind of the same summary enough that could be another option because it's a
beautiful dress I have a brown corset from Lou yeah something brown
Because that makes you look good.
pretty dress the only thing is that at the time i got it shortened and
the guy took too much oh no way because it's too short it's a little
bit but i still wear it because um when i got it shortened it didn't
have the wrap oh my god i didn't bring it up and when i wrapped
it i was like oh no and remember we got it um embroidery embroidered each
dress had a number embroidered If any of you watch this channel and has this
dress, let me know in the comments.
I'd love to know because this is like such a beautiful piece.
Is it a piece we should redo?
You guys, I was trying this and I was like, this is a sleeve?
No.
This is not a sleeve.
Sorry, it's a wrap.
Okay, I think this dress could actually be really beautiful.
The back is insane.
It's kind of gorgeous.
You can actually do that.
Oh, that's nicer.
See?
That's better.
and i think it's meant to be like that yeah it's a very sexy dress
and it's very it's hot it's italy dolce vita vibes no yeah restaurants in a
five star hotel yeah vibes then do i try the dress that everyone knows and
have seen a hundred thousand times oh my god i i you know what i'm
gonna try because i want to see if i'm gonna wear it because if i
don't wear it i'll leave it here second option very classic we all know this
one but this is like easy sexy beautiful orange looks so good what do we
do i just bought these pants at imgia it's very like thin pants but i
kind of like it i like the
you know it's a little too short for me but pants are usually a little
too short for me so i'm just gonna make it a little longer there's some
extra fabric at the bottom but do we love the detail of the belt look
right it's fun it's like a different little type of okay i love
and we have arrived in
we are now heading out to the hotel which is always a pressure for me
because I booked it online and you never know what it's going to look like.
I want it to be nice.
And I also have a reputation.
I have a reputation with my boyfriend or my family that I always choose good
hotels and good restaurants.
So I have a reputation to keep up with.
And so pressure is on.
We're living life!
We checked in the hotel, we went to the pool, and then we got ready,
and then we were in the cab and the sunset was insane so we were
like drop us off at this bridge so we went to the bridge we watched
the sunset and then we started walking in the little streets and we saw all
these people having drinks living their life we were like we want to live our
life like them so we went there and we had drinks and we had amazing
like little charcuterie cheese boards not cheese She's played.
Isn't it fabulous?
It's 10 p.m.
and we're going for a late dinner because we're so Italian!
Good
morning
and welcome to a new show called Boobs and Sandwich.
we just got out of the hotel and we're starving and so we
got some little sandwiches
this is gonna be fabulous this one is mortadella and this one is prosciutto crudo
and it's gonna be so good we went to al antico vinayo which apparently is
like famous spots
We
just had lunch and now we decided to have a little Ahogato at Vivolo, which
is kind of a famous spot to have it here in Piedmont.
Fun fact about me, I've never had an Ahogato before.
Really?
Ever.
This is my first one.
Cheers to your first one.
Cheers.
Wow!
This is sweet.
Okay, change of plans.
We were walking around and we just passed by this tattoo shop and my boyfriend's
like, I'm getting one.
actually had spot for a walk-in so we're getting not me not me he's getting
a small tattoo
this is the tattoo place we went to and the guy's name was met and
he was so sweet and so so professional okay tattoo done the meaning of this
word is souris souris in french means mouse um and it's actually his nickname for
me and i have it for him too he started calling me souris right at
the beginning of us dating and so there we go he's a souris forever and
i was saying funny enough it's something that i had forgotten when i was a
kid i used to watch a italian show called, Italian show called Topoggio, which was
this little mouse.
And I was saying that I actually love the word Topolino to say mouse in
Italian.
So there we are.
All about mouse today.
We're now walking.
It's 4 p.m.
and we are walking to a little vintage shop that I saw on the map.
I'm gonna go see if we can find any type of treasure.
My boyfriend's like we're gonna buy you a dress today.
I'm like you're being very very
how do we say?
Very ambitious.
Like I always go to vintage shops with no expectation.
Yes.
Gucci pants.
Look at this.
They're more than...
They're really warm.
It's amazing.
You guys, look at this pair of Chanel jeans.
I think we're gonna go try them.
I said no to this.
But actually now that he's worn it, it's cute cute.
I'm gonna try this Roberto Cavalli pants.
I love the detail at the bottom.
And of course, I'm gonna try the Gucci one.
That's number one.
So, look at that.
It's a bottle.
Yep.
It's a beautiful piece.
It's not good.
Oh la la!
You fit in these.
Yeah.
Nobody fits in these.
Okay.
You can make it tighter from here, look.
Yeah, I maxed it to the...
Are they low-waisted?
Yes, they're early 2000.
They're early 2000 Cavalli.
Simple.
And that's the style.
Bellissimo.
That's why I said they fit you perfectly.
They go...
I am thinking about them.
These are gorgeous.
They're low-waisted.
This insane tattoo detail into the leather.
The color is insane.
Richie.
I'm trying on the Gucci pants.
The Gucci pants.
They're insane, but they're extremely uncomfortable.
Very long.
Here it's too big, so definitely a no, but I had to try it.
Look at this.
I am on a fashion high.
We are on a fashion.
I'm on a fashion.
I'm high on fashion.
I got the pants, guys.
i got the pants and he got the top and he got a pants and
he got a pair and not a jacket of jeans jacket levi's jeans jacket i
feel like pretty woman you we are really a version of pretty woman honestly the
store was so good there was all types of prices of course if you go
into the chanel and roberto cavalli alaya it's a little bit more pricey but still
you know the chanel pants I showed you the jeans it was 500 euros it's
not that expensive for a Chanel vintage piece
so really nice and then in the back of the store you have like more
affordable brands so there's a little bit of everything for everyone and then John Franco
the owner of the store was so sweet we had amazing conversation and the store
sweet nothing sweet sweet doing sweet doing Street doing vintage couture.
Good morning guys and happy Sunday.
We stayed in bed until like 1 pm.
We were watching the QALYs, the F1 QALYs, Monaco Grand Prix from yesterday and we
are now heading out for lunch.
we found a little Osteria that looks fabulous so we hope we get there in
time because they're actually closing soon and then we are just going to stroll around
we have the full day ahead of us since we leave only tomorrow morning so
we're planning on spending the whole day in Firenze we're having a huge dilemma because
at 3 p.m you have the Roland Garros finals and at 3 p.m you have
the F1 race so we're like trying to pick what we're gonna be following.
Guys I'm wearing the pants.
Once we get out of this car, let me show you my look with the
pants.
It is officially one of my favorite pieces purchased in 2026.
We
need
to watch at least the beginning of the race.
Thank
you.
Good
evening.
So we went back to the hotel to chill a little bit because it was
really warm and now we're out again.
Someone that I met recently at an event is actually here in Firenze.
He is a painter.
His name is Georgios and he is doing like a live painting event.
So we are going to go pass by to see what it's all about.
And then we have many spots we want to hit.
We have a dinner reservation, but before we're going to have a drink, maybe on
a rooftop, we want to have a drink again at the first place we went
to the first night here.
And that's it.
And we've just been really enjoying it.
Okay, that was quick.
It was so funny.
I was extremely nervous to be painting live, which I understand.
And now on to our next stop, which we're going to go get a drink
at Il Santino.
It was the first spot we went to the first night by walking by.
And it looked nice.
We stopped for a drink.
And ever since, we're like, we need to go back one more time.
We loved the vibe.
So we are going there.
my boyfriend has been committed into creating a reels for me.
You guys, he's been filming me in all ways in the cities, being like, I'm
going to do like a paparazzi vibe reels.
Don't look at me.
He's been running, making me cross.
He's at the moment choosing the music, editing.
So cute.
I'm executive producer.
He's an executive producer.
He's like let me do a real for you.
I edit it.
I choose the song.
I said do it whatever, you know So you'll see the results on instagram.
You can go there on instagram and check it out and forget the credits Don't
forget.
I will credit you hours of work hours of work.
I'll credit you So yes, so like this you show some love to him and
his work his masterpiece.
Yes
You guys, so these pants are from the vintage shop yesterday.
He is in love with the details.
Look at that, look at that, look at that.
Okay, oh the butt, yes, yes.
Vibes and my pants are from the vintage shop.
So here we go.
We are now walking to our
final destination, which is the dinner.
It is actually recommended by one of you guys that wrote to me on Instagram
and said that next door to Isantino there was a very good restaurant.
So that's where we're having dinner tonight, which I don't even remember the name anymore.
We're having dinner there.
Dream table.
We are back into the hotel room.
We're actually packing because tomorrow we are heading back to Paris on a 6 a.m.
flight.
We're not going to Paris.
We wish we could stay longer, but we have to go home.
And so this is the end of the vlog and I thought I'd do something
different.
I always end the vlog saying I wish you all a beautiful day or a
beautiful night wherever you are.
And this time I'm going to do it in Italian.
Are we guys ready?
Are we ready?
Is Italy ready to hear that, people?
Ti auguro una splendida giornata o una splendida notte ovunque
tu sia.
Bellissima.
And I'll catch you guys.
in my next video bye guys